{"categoryID":1,"question":"Is he small?","answer":"Yes.","animal":"ant","f1":"small","f2":"strong","f3":"busy"},
{"categoryID":2,"question":"Is he scary?","answer":"Yes.","animal":"bat","f1":"scary","f2":"blind","f3":"nocturnal"},
{"categoryID":3,"question":"Is he scary?","answer":"Yes.","animal":"bear","f1":"scary","f2":"big","f3":"fierce"},
{"categoryID":4,"question":"Is he busy?","answer":"Yes.","animal":"bee","f1":"busy","f2":"small","f3":"angry"},
{"categoryID":5,"question":"Is he small?","answer":"Yes.","animal":"bird","f1":"small","f2":"graceful","f3":"free"},
{"categoryID":6,"question":"Is he big?","answer":"Yes.","animal":"buffalo","f1":"big","f2":"strong","f3":"wild"},
{"categoryID":7,"question":"Is he independent?","answer":"Yes.","animal":"cat","f1":"independent","f2":"lazy","f3":"soft"},
{"categoryID":8,"question":"Is he fat?","answer":"Yes.","animal":"cow","f1":"fat","f2":"lazy","f3":"dumb"},
{"categoryID":9,"question":"Is he loyal?","answer":"Yes.","animal":"dog","f1":"loyal","f2":"friendly","f3":"happy"},
{"categoryID":10,"question":"Is he smart?","answer":"Yes.","animal":"dolphin","f1":"smart","f2":"friendly","f3":"playful"},
{"categoryID":11,"question":"Is he loud?","answer":"Yes.","animal":"duck","f1":"loud","f2":"cute","f3":"quacking"},
{"categoryID":12,"question":"Is he huge?","answer":"Yes.","animal":"elephant","f1":"huge","f2":"smart","f3":"heavy"},
{"categoryID":13,"question":"Is he scaly?","answer":"Yes.","animal":"fish","f1":"scaly","f2":"wet","f3":"smelly"},
{"categoryID":14,"question":"Is he sly?","answer":"Yes.","animal":"fox","f1":"sly","f2":"smart","f3":"pretty"},
{"categoryID":15,"question":"Is he slimy?","answer":"Yes.","animal":"frog","f1":"slimy","f2":"noisy","f3":"jumpy"},
{"categoryID":16,"question":"Is he funny?","answer":"Yes.","animal":"goat","f1":"funny","f2":"hungry","f3":"loud"},
{"categoryID":17,"question":"Is he loud?","answer":"Yes.","animal":"goose","f1":"loud","f2":"mean","f3":"annoying"},
{"categoryID":18,"question":"Is he fast?","answer":"Yes.","animal":"horse","f1":"fast","f2":"strong","f3":"beautiful"},
{"categoryID":19,"question":"Is he jumpy?","answer":"Yes.","animal":"kangaroo","f1":"jumpy","f2":"bouncy","f3":"cute"},
{"categoryID":20,"question":"Is he scary?","answer":"Yes.","animal":"lion","f1":"scary","f2":"strong","f3":"ferocious"},
{"categoryID":21,"question":"Is he funny?","answer":"Yes.","animal":"monkey","f1":"funny","f2":"smart","f3":"playful"},
{"categoryID":22,"question":"Is he wise?","answer":"Yes.","animal":"owl","f1":"wise","f2":"quiet","f3":"nocturnal"},
{"categoryID":23,"question":"Is he strong?","answer":"Yes.","animal":"ox","f1":"strong","f2":"big","f3":"slow"},
{"categoryID":24,"question":"Is he cold?","answer":"Yes.","animal":"penguin","f1":"cold","f2":"cute","f3":"funny"},
{"categoryID":25,"question":"Is he dirty?","answer":"Yes.","animal":"pig","f1":"dirty","f2":"fat","f3":"smelly"},
{"categoryID":26,"question":"Is he fast?","answer":"Yes.","animal":"rabbit","f1":"fast","f2":"furry","f3":"cute"},
{"categoryID":27,"question":"Is he scary?","answer":"Yes.","animal":"shark","f1":"scary","f2":"mean","f3":"dangerous"},
{"categoryID":28,"question":"Is he wooly?","answer":"Yes.","animal":"sheep","f1":"wooly","f2":"fluffy","f3":"dumb"},
{"categoryID":29,"question":"Is he striped?","answer":"Yes.","animal":"tiger","f1":"striped","f2":"fierce","f3":"scary"},
{"categoryID":30,"question":"Is he large?","answer":"Yes.","animal":"whale","f1":"large","f2":"graceful","f3":"majestic"},
{"categoryID":31,"question":"Is he scary?","answer":"Yes.","animal":"wolf","f1":"scary","f2":"mean","f3":"angry"},
{"categoryID":32,"question":"Is he striped?","answer":"Yes.","animal":"zebra","f1":"striped","f2":"exotic","f3":"fast"},
